http://www.phonydiploma.com/privacy.aspx

WE ARE ABOUT TRUST AND TRANSPARENCY! SEE OUR REVIEWS AND BUY THE BEST REPLACEMENT HIGH SCHOOL, COLLEGE DIPLOMAS, TRANSCRIPTS & DEGREES
0
Buy NowHigh School & SecondaryHigh School DiplomasHigh School Transcript RecordsHigh School Diploma & Transcript SetsCollege and University Diplomas & TranscriptsUSACanadaAustraliaNew ZealandUnited KingdomSouth AfricaMalaysiaSingaporeIndonesiaThailandVietnamTurkeyFranceItalyIrelandPhilippinesMexicoRussiaSpainIndiaArgentinaBelizeBrazilCaribbeanChileChinaColumbiaCosta-RicaCroatiaDenmarkEgyptGermanyGreeceGuatemalaIsraelKazakhstanLebanonNetherlandsNorwayPanamaSwedenSwitzerlandUnited Arab EmiratesRequest A Free SampleOther DocumentsCertificatesReprintsCustom Match Diplomas & TranscriptsTranscriptsDiplomasEmblem, Seal Upgrade: DiplomaFAQSEE A SAMPLESamplesGuaranteeShippingReviewsPaperEmblemsPaymentsBlogWe Dont DoTermsSupport
0
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note, the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By E-Mail: support@docprinters.com
By Text: (917) 746-5875
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
How Can We Help?
Frequent Questions
Why Choose Phonydiploma?How Does This Work?Degrees & MajorsPaper & FoldersSignaturesPayment OptionsDelivery TurnaroundOrder Status UpdatesWhat We Don't PrintSteps To Place An Order
High School Order Forms
DiplomasDiploma & TranscriptTranscript Only
USA College Order Forms
Original Match DiplomaHouse Design DiplomaOriginal Match TranscriptHouse Design TranscriptOriginal Match Diploma & Original Match TranscriptOriginal Match Diploma & House Design TranscriptHouse Design Diploma & House Design Transcript
International Order Forms
Original Match DiplomasOriginal Match Diploma & Original Match TranscriptOriginal Match Diploma &
House Design Transcript
International Samples
AfricaAustraliaCanadaEgyptFranceGermanyIndiaItalyMalaysiaNetherlandsNew ZealandSingaporeTurkeySpainSpanish LanguageUKAll Countries Map
Other Diploma Order Forms
Reprints of Previous OrdersCustom EmblemsCustom Upgrades
More Information
Paper and FoldersAfter You OrderCancel & Refund PolicyCredit Card DisputesDisclaimerView Diploma DesignsTerms and ConditionsData Security and Privacy
Brought to you by SiteJabber
Frequent Questions
Why Choose Phonydiploma?How Does This Work?Degrees & MajorsPaper & FoldersSignaturesPayment OptionsDelivery TurnaroundOrder Status UpdatesWhat We Don't PrintSteps To Place An Order
More Information
Paper and FoldersAfter You OrderCancel & Refund PolicyCredit Card DisputesDisclaimerView Diploma DesignsTerms and ConditionsData Security and Privacy
High School Order Forms
DiplomasDiploma & TranscriptTranscript Only
USA College Order Forms
Original Match DiplomaHouse Design DiplomaOriginal Match TranscriptHouse Design TranscriptOriginal Match Diploma & Original Match TranscriptOriginal Match Diploma & House Design TranscriptHouse Design Diploma & House Design Transcript
International Order Forms
Original Match DiplomasOriginal Match Diploma & Original Match TranscriptOriginal Match Diploma &
House Design Transcript
International Samples
AfricaAustraliaCanadaEgyptFranceGermanyIndiaItalyMalaysiaNetherlandsNew ZealandSingaporeTurkeySpainSpanish LanguageUKAll Countries Map
Other Diploma Order Forms
Reprints of Previous OrdersCustom EmblemsCustom Upgrades
Frequent Questions
Why Choose Phonydiploma?
How Does This work?
Degrees and Majors
Paper and Folders
Signatures
Payment Options
Delivery Turnaround
Order Status Updates
What We Don't Print
Steps To Place An Order
PhonyDiploma Testimonials
Arabic | Chinese | Espanol | French | German | Hindi | Italian | Malay | Turkish | Vietnamese
Other Pages
Buy High School and College Diplomas
Buy High School and College Transcripts
Buy High School & College Diploma & Transcripts
Reprints of Previous Orders
Custom Emblems
Custom Upgrades
Transcripts FAQs
Click Here
At Phonydiploma.com we offer fast delivery of professional-quality fake high school, fake college, fake university diplomas and fake transcripts. We do everything possible to ensure your package is the most realistic looking and feeling fake diploma reproduction available.
We individually design your order to your specifications and print using professional quality equipment. Then, add emblems, logos, seals and stamps using metal die embossers, gold-foil stickers, rubber stamps, raised “puffy” ink emblems, holograms and more. We ship worldwide via UPS and USPS with door-to-door tracking. Neither the packaging box nor your credit card receipt will say anything about the nature of your product.
We offer an extensive database of “actual match” diplomas and transcripts as the foundation of your design. If we don’t have the exact design, we have general designs that can be customized with almost any school name.
We’re available by toll-free telephone, online chat and email and answer your questions promptly and professionally. We’re proud of our high ranking in multiple customer review sites and our 12-year history of providing the best novelty diploma and transcript reproductions available worldwide.
More Info
Copyright 2020 © Phonydiploma.com, Doc Printers
Realistic Diplomas
Same Day Diplomas
Fraud Policy
Privacy Policy
Terms
Contact
Please Wait...
